Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Digital Documents
  - University of Michigan Presidency, 1986-1997; 5397 original digital files (393 MB)
    - Position Papers, 1986-1997; 140 original digital files
      - 1991-1996 Position Papers, 66 files
        - Rackham-edited, 2016
        - Research U Speech-MSU 1-23-96, 2016
        - Appro Hearings 0.9, 2016
        - CostPriceValue 2.1, 2016
        - The Road Ahead, 2016
        - Georgia Tech-Text, 2016
        - Mission Statement 0.9, 2016
        - Transformation Text 1.6 wd5, 2016
        - 1991-1997 Position Papers Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Operating Manual 1.1, 2016
        - Senate Hearing 2.1, 3/15/1992
        - Technology Policy Text, 3/16/1992
        - TV-Students, 3/17/1992
        - State of Univ 1993, 3/2/1994
        - State of Univ 1993 1.1, 3/2/1994
        - Sports-Falls Response-Hot, 3/20/1994
        - Sports-Falls Response-Mild, 3/20/1994
        - JJD Essay (Research) 1.3, 3/24/1992
        - JJD Essay (Research) 1.0, 3/24/1992
        - Transformation CIC 2.1, 3/28/1994
        - Transformation CIC 2.2, 3/28/1994
        - Women 3.3, 3/31/1994
        - Women Ex Sum 3.2, 3/7/1994
        - Themes for 175th, 3/8/1992
        - Women 3.2, 3/8/1994
        - OpEd Pipeline 2.2, 4/22/1992
        - Strategic History 2.0, 4/25/1993
        - Strategic History 2.1, 4/25/1993
        - Women 3.4, 4/8/1994
        - Net '92, 4/9/1992
        - MICH MAND 3YR UPDATE 1.0, 5/16/1991
        - ASIS Talk, 5/23/1994
        - Strategic Marketing Plan, 5/3/1991
        - PC Address 1.1, 5/30/1991
        - Position memo, 5/30/1992
        - ITIC Statement, 5/31/1992
        - Agenda 1.2, 6/29/1994
        - Mandate History 1.1, 6/6/1991
        - Mandate History 1.2, 6/6/1991
        - China Odyssey, 6/8/1993
        - Agenda 1.31, 7/20/1994
        - CASE 1.0, 8/12/1992
        - MM Update 1.3, 8/29/1991
        - Public Service 3.1, 8/3/1992
        - Kickoff 1.0, 9/10/1992
        - Kellogg Letter Proposal, 9/11/1994
        - MM Update letter 1.4, 9/4/1991
      - 1996-1997 Position Papers, 04 files
    - Presentations, 1987-1997; 64 original digital files
      The majority of records in the Presentations subseries (64 original digital files, 1987-1996) were created using the software application PowerPoint by Microsoft. This application was designed specifically as a presentation tool. Many of the records in this series seem to be presentations given to Duderstadt's Executive Officers (EOs) and the Regents at retreat meetings (for example, 'Regents Retreat,' 'Tuition Retreat,' 'Leadership Retreat'). Other presentation topics included in this series are The Michigan Mandate, The Mission Plan, and University Resources.
      Researchers will note that in the University of Michigan Presidency series contextual and descriptive information such as audience, location, and exact date of the presentation or speech is not always explicit in the digital record.
      - 1987-1988 Presentations, 1 files
        - Science Education, 1/14/1990
        - Resources for the 1990s, 1/4/1991
        - Communication, 1/6/1990
        - Transformation Course, 1/7/1994
        - Campaign--11/89, 10/17/1989
        - Vision 2017 Pres 1.0, 11/10/1993
        - Michigan Mandate 2.2, 11/20/1988
        - EVPHA Presentation, 11/20/1994
        - Michigan Mandate 2.2C, 11/21/1988
        - Eye on the Ball-II, 11/5/1990
        - Academic Affairs-1/88, 12/27/1987
        - Tuition Retreat, 12/6/1989
        - Business Plan-1990s, 2/17/1990
        - Slides-Resources for the 1990's, 2/25/1991
        - White-Resources for the 1990's, 2/28/1991
        - Strategic Planning Update, 2/3/1992
        - The Top Ten, 2/3/1992
        - Campaign Ideas 1.0, 2/4/1989
        - Regent Priorities, 2/5/1991
        - JJD PAG presentation, 2016
        - 1987-1995 Presentations-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Mission Statement, 3/11/1988
        - Eye on the Ball, 3/12/1990
        - Athenaeum, 3/5/1991
        - Campaign-Color, 4/11/1990
        - Mission-35mm, 4/18/1988
        - Campaign-Color-update, 4/18/1990
        - Community Outreach, 4/26/1989
        - YNH Projects, 4/3/1991
        - Campaign Briefing-1990, 4/6/1990
        - Economics Dinner Group, 4/6/1990
        - FY88-89 Budget-(5/88), 5/16/1988
        - Regents Resources, 5/20/1996
        - State Support, 5/24/1989
        - Strategic Marketing, 5/29/1991
        - Campaign GoNoGo, 5/7/1990
        - NSB-6/90, 6/11/1990
        - UM Organization, 6/23/1990
        - Michigan Mandate-Color, 6/6/1992
        - Resources Update, 6/8/1995
        - Resources Update-11, 6/8/1995
        - Resources, 6/9/1995
        - Futures/Missions, 7/20/1991
        - Regents Retreat, 7/8/1989
        - Title List, 8/29/1990
        - The Plan Itself 1.1, 8/30/1991
        - EO Retreat (Fall-91), 8/30/1991
        - Futuring, 8/30/1991
        - EO Retreat-93, 8/30/1991
        - EO Strategic Update, 8/30/1991
        - Transformation Course 2, 8/30/1996
        - Transformation Course 1, 8/30/1996
        - Millennium Seminar, 8/31/1996
        - Leadership Retreat, 9/1/1989
        - Futures Group 1.0, 9/1/1991
        - State Strategy-89, 9/11/1989
        - Leadership Retreat-F90, 9/3/1990
      - 1988-1989 Presentations, 5 files
      - 1989-1990 Presentations, 8 files
      - 1990-1991 Presentations, 13 files
      - 1991-1992 Presentations, 17 files
      - 1992-1993 Presentations, 3 files
      - 1993-1994 Presentations, 1 files
      - 1994-1995 Presentations, 2 files
      - 1995-1996 Presentations, 3 files
      - 1996-1997 Presentations, 11 files
    - Write Files, 1988-1997; 588 original digital files
      The Write Files subseries (588 original digital files, 1987-1997) is composed entirely of Microsoft Word text files. Researchers will find a variety of 'traditional' business formats such as correspondence, agendas, and memorandums contained within the Write Files series. However, note that there is often an absence of descriptive information, such as the receiver's name and address, date, and signature line. The absence of this information is a reflection of the distributive work process practiced in President Duderstadt's office--a process afforded by networked computer technology. The correspondence includes letters of recommendation, thank-you's, and communication to persons not only at the University of Michigan but to persons throughout the country including U.S. presidents Gerald Ford and George Bush and Michigan governors James Blanchard and John Engler. It is important to note that Duderstadt often used the recipient's name or initials to name the file. For example, 'Blanchard-1/89' and 'H & V-11/10' are communications to Governor James Blanchard in January 1989 and Harold and Vivian Shapiro on November 10th respectively.
      - 1988 and earlier Write Files, 19 files
        - Regents-1/88, 1/12/1988
        - Regents-3/87, 1/12/1988
        - Development Priorities, 1/24/1988
        - Yale-10/88, 10/8/1988
        - Racism Retreat-12/87, 11/26/1987
        - H&V-11/10, 11/6/1987
        - Racism-II, 2/2/1988
        - Commencement, 2016
        - 1988 and earlier Write Files-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - UMMC Leadership, 2016
        - Questions, 2016
        - Regents Handouts, 5/12/1987
        - Regents Handouts-II, 5/13/1987
        - Luggage Tags, 6/17/1988
        - Shortt-7/11, 7/11/1988
        - Football Wk-7/11, 7/11/1988
        - 88-89 Budget Draft #2, 7/12/1988
        - Jim' 8/21/88, 8/21/1988
        - Poster Titles, 8/24/1988
        - Diversity Retreat, 8/27/1987
        - Diversity Overheads, 9/2/1987
        - 25 Year, 9/28/1987
        - Roosevelt, 9/7/1988
      - 1988-1989 Write Files, 19 files
        - Costs Task Force, 1/16/1989
        - Hornback, 1/18/1989
        - Blanchard-1/89, 1/20/1989
        - EO Internal, 1/22/1989
        - House Memo-1/29/89, 1/29/1989
        - Chick Fisher, 11/10/1988
        - Giles-11/14, 11/14/1988
        - Ford-12/19, 12/19/1988
        - Commen Recept, 12/7/1988
        - EO Regents, 2/15/1989
        - Academy, 2/16/1989
        - Ford-2/89, 2/22/1989
        - Fleming, 2/7/1989
        - 1990s Campaign, 2016
        - Detroit-3_30, 2016
        - Frats-3/89, 3/20/1989
        - CMU Search, 3/22/1989
        - Holcombe-3/89, 3/7/1989
        - Friday, 4/26/1989
        - Holcombe-5/4/89, 5/4/1989
        - Comm Ideas, 6/11/1989
      - 1989-1990 Write Files, 50 files
        - Weidenbach-1/90, 1/12/1990
        - P.C. - Forums Speech, 1/15/1990
        - CEO Meeting, 1/17/1990
        - P.C. - Forums Speech 1.1, 1/18/1990
        - Bob Alexander, 1/22/1990
        - JFB Nom, 1/22/1990
        - Michigan-1990, 1/22/1990
        - Elmer Lewis, 1/24/1990
        - Leadership Checklist, 1/29/1990
        - EO Structure-PC, 1/31/1990
        - Simon, 1/31/1990
        - EO Structure (S), 1/4/1990
        - PIF-90, 1/6/1990
        - Solomon-1/90, 1/7/1990
        - Michigan Rankings, 1/8/1990
        - Roundtable, 1/9/1990
        - Letters-10/89, 10/16/1989
        - Case Statement, 10/18/1989
        - Akers, 10/18/1989
        - Regents-Educom, 10/20/1989
        - Endow Comp, 10/26/1989
        - AAU Toronto, 10/28/1991
        - State Brochure 2, 10/29/1989
        - State Brochure, 10/29/1989
        - Develop Structure, 10/3/1989
        - State Agreement, 11/13/1989
        - Iacocca-12/89, 11/29/1989
        - House Update, 11/5/1989
        - JJD Assessment, 11/5/1989
        - Bo, 12/13/1989
        - Knoll, 12/15/1989
        - Penn State, 12/19/1989
        - EO Structure, 12/21/1989
        - Kellogg, 2/13/1990
        - Survey, 2/13/1990
        - Roundtable - List, 2/14/1990
        - Dumas, 2/20/1990
        - MMCC, 2/21/1990
        - BB, 2/27/1990
        - Minority Graphs, 2/3/1990
        - D'Arms-3/19/90, 3/19/1990
        - BAM, 4/3/1990
        - Penn State-Q&A, 5/14/1990
        - Michigan Roundtable, 5/21/1990
        - Roger Smith, 5/8/1990
        - Regents-CMV, 6/11/1990
        - Cambridge Thanks, 7/10/1989
        - Activity Summary, 7/10/1989
        - Citizens Res Council, 9/20/1989
        - State Strategy, 9/9/1989
      - 1990-1991 Write Files, 74 files
        - Inglis Memo II, 1/10/1991
        - Mawby, 1/24/1991
        - Research VP, 10/1/1990
        - Budget Issues, 10/15/1990
        - NSB EHR Study, 10/15/1990
        - R vs T, 10/23/1990
        - Medical School, 10/31/1990
        - NoCode, 11/18/1990
        - Jjd e-mail, 11/19/1990
        - Brown-11/19, 11/19/1990
        - PC-Safety, 11/19/1990
        - Student letter, 11/19/1990
        - JJD Student Letter, 11/21/1990
        - Inglis House policy, 11/23/1990
        - Inglis House 3.1, 11/24/1990
        - Inglis House III, 11/24/1990
        - RLK Organization, 11/5/1990
        - Schultz, 11/6/1990
        - Lamar Alexander, 12/18/1990
        - Regents-12/19/90, 12/19/1990
        - Big Ten, 12/2/1990
        - Pres Spouse II, 12/25/1990
        - Anita's Memo, 12/3/1990
        - PCV Proposal, 2/11/1991
        - Futures Group, 2/20/1991
        - Manoogian, 2/21/1991
        - Hockaday-2/91, 2/6/1991
        - Engler-2/91, 2/6/1991
        - Madden-2/91, 2/6/1991
        - Prector-2/91, 2/6/1991
        - MNET, 2/7/1991
        - Regents-2/91, 2/8/1991
        - Mrs. Bush_AMD, 2016
        - Moses-3_91, 2016
        - DC Notes-9_12, 2016
        - 1990-1991 Write Files-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Engler Meeting-3/91, 3/11/1991
        - Hilgert, 3/12/1991
        - NCAA Testimony, 3/25/1991
        - B. Ruppel, 3/25/1991
        - Rudenstine, 3/25/1991
        - Lohman, 3/27/1991
        - Bechtel, 3/7/1991
        - Bga/notes-2, 3/7/1991
        - Mike Ada., 3/8/1991
        - Roosevelt Quote, 3/8/1991
        - Regents-Faculty, 4/2/1991
        - Futures, 4/29/1991
        - Affirm Action, 4/29/1991
        - President Bush/JJD, 5/15/1991
        - ICR, 5/21/1991
        - Regents-Tuition, 5/22/1991
        - Strategic Marketing Plan 1.1, 5/3/1991
        - Ford, 5/31/1991
        - Teeter-June, 5/31/1991
        - Nat'l media, 5/9/1991
        - Big Ten List, 6/1/1991
        - Eotvos-6/91, 6/10/1991
        - Fasing-6/91, 6/10/1991
        - Green-6/91, 6/10/1991
        - Engler-6/91, 6/10/1991
        - Gov Rel Structure 1.0, 6/10/1991
        - Traxler-6/91, 6/10/1991
        - CMV Comment, 6/11/1990
        - Some notes, 6/18/1991
        - UM Tuition, 6/18/1991
        - SS Report Card, 6/22/1991
        - PC Regents Memo, 6/24/1991
        - MICH MANDATE 3 YR UPDATE, 6/26/1991
        - GW-Provost, 7/11/1990
        - EO Salaries, 7/28/1990
        - Gilmour, 7/30/1990
        - Blanchard-8/90, 7/31/1990
        - HTS-8/90, 7/5/1990
        - Provost Search, 7/9/1990
      - 1991-1992 Write Files, 54 files
        - Regents-House, 1/13/1992
        - Regents-Challenges, 1/13/1992
        - Teeter, 1/21/1992
        - Cosovich, 1/4/1992
        - FWC Letter, 1/4/1992
        - Farhat, 1/5/1992
        - Ritz-Carlton, 1/5/1992
        - Rose Bowl Letters, 1/6/1992
        - Hornback-1/92, 1/9/1992
        - VPSS, 10/18/1991
        - MET Board, 10/28/1991
        - Elsa Cole, 10/7/1991
        - Daily Ad Response, 11/1/1991
        - GUIR Review, 11/1/1991
        - HTS-11/91, 11/12/1991
        - Regents-11/91, 11/15/1991
        - Futures-Autonomy, 12/10/1991
        - MET Observations, 12/11/1991
        - Regents Discussion (12/91), 12/19/1991
        - Deane Baker-12/91, 12/2/1991
        - Modem Info, 12/20/1991
        - Senate Assembly ll/l9/9l, 12/3/1991
        - Power-12/91, 12/5/1991
        - Cehelsky-2/92, 2/10/1992
        - Campaign Restructuring, 2/10/1992
        - Inge, 2/12/1992
        - Darman-2/92, 2/19/1992
        - Innkeeping Notice, 2/6/1992
        - External Relations Word, 2016
        - Duke-3/92, 3/18/1992
        - Lang-3/92, 3/6/1992
        - Krumm-4/92, 4/1/1992
        - Hasselmo-4/92, 4/8/1992
        - MC Parking, 5/11/1992
        - Cunningham-5/92, 5/12/1992
        - Futures-5/92, 5/18/1992
        - PCSUM-5/92, 5/18/1992
        - Position memo, 5/30/1992
        - ITIC Statement, 5/31/1992
        - College Sports 1.0, 6/13/1992
        - Harwit, 6/16/1992
        - Teeter, (7/10/91), 7/10/1991
        - Regents Annual Report 1.2, 7/16/1991
        - Traxler, 7/17/1991
        - Traineeship, 7/18/1991
        - CUE Report, 7/20/1991
        - National Rankings, 7/21/1991
        - AAU Letter1.1, 7/24/1991
        - Regents Cover Letter, 7/27/1991
        - CDM, 7/3/1991
        - CDM/sac edit, 7/3/1991
        - Football Invites, 7/30/1991
        - Grady-II, 7/4/1991
        - Regents Tuition Briefing, 7/5/1991
        - Campaign Kickoff, 9/15/1991
      - 1992-1993 Write Files, 120 files
        - Governor's Strategy 1.0, 1/18/1993
        - NSB Report, 1/18/1993
        - Football Championship, 1/19/1993
        - NSB E-mail, 1/25/1993
        - Bowen-1/93, 1/26/1993
        - OTA-1/93, 1/26/1993
        - VPR Search Committee, 1/29/1993
        - PB 1.1, 1/4/1993
        - PB 1.0, 1/4/1993
        - Redrawing Boundaries 3.1, 1/6/1993
        - Gateway College 2.0, 1/7/1993
        - CJ Dialog, 10/13/1992
        - JJD Essay (Sports) 2.2, 10/14/1992
        - JJD Essay (Teaching) 1.0, 10/18/1992
        - Intellectual Change 2.2, 10/22/1992
        - Vision 2000 1.7, 10/25/1993
        - Regents Meetings, 10/28/1992
        - EO Letters (cont), 10/7/1992
        - Joe/Jon, 11/11/1992
        - E-mail notes, 11/13/1992
        - Joe/Jon II, 11/25/1992
        - Gateway College, 11/25/1992
        - Progress Report, 11/27/1992
        - Vision Statement, 11/27/1992
        - RPI-11/92, 11/6/1992
        - Eng M&S, 12/18/1992
        - Neal-12/92, 12/23/1992
        - Fin Aid Op-Ed 2.0, 12/26/1992
        - Regents Meeting Memo, 12/7/1992
        - Progress Report, 1992-11-27
        - NSF Director, 2/15/1993
        - Gibbons-2/93, 2/3/1993
        - Ehrlich1, 2/4/1991
        - Financial Aid 1.0, 2/5/1993
        - Ba, 2016
        - 1991-92 Summary, 2016
        - CEO Compensation Table, 2016
        - 1992-1993 Write Files-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Comp Study, 3/16/1993
        - DEVH-3/93, 3/16/1993
        - Woodworth-3/93, 3/16/1993
        - Shalala-3/93, 3/22/1993
        - Alexander-3/93, 3/4/1993
        - Budget Proposal, 3/9/1993
        - Notebook Data 1.1, 4/14/1993
        - E-mail-4/93, 4/20/1993
        - JJD Rec, 4/25/1993
        - Strategic History 1.6, 4/25/1993
        - Academic Leadership 1.1, 4/27/1992
        - Webber, 4/9/1993
        - DB Attacks, 5/20/1992
        - Brown-5/93, 5/3/1993
        - Bobette-5/93, 5/5/1993
        - Gibbons-5/93, 5/5/1993
        - NSB-facilities, 5/6/1993
        - UM-Flint-a5/93, 5/6/1993
        - Metrics, 6/10/1993
        - Sal Comp, 6/14/1993
        - Moses Reference, 6/16/1993
        - EO Counts, 6/27/1993
        - UM-UC-UT Comp, 6/27/1993
        - Admin Cost Comp, 7/1/1993
        - Day-7/92, 7/10/1992
        - Peterson-7/92, 7/17/1992
        - Inglis House 3.2, 7/18/1992
        - President's House 1.2, 7/18/1992
        - OUE Memo 7/2, 7/2/1992
        - EO Salary Letters, 7/20/1993
        - Staff Salaries, 7/21/1993
        - HTS-UMMC, 7/3/1993
        - Presidential Events 2.1, 7/30/1992
        - BHEF Ideas, 7/6/1992
        - Presidential Candidates, 7/6/1993
        - Rauch-7/8, 7/8/1992
        - Shankar-7/7, 7/8/1992
        - EO Restructuring, 7/8/1993
        - Regents-AD Search, 8/10/1993
        - CASE 1.0, 8/12/1992
        - Inglis/Pres Use Memo 2.0, 8/18/1992
        - Inglis House 2.0, 8/18/1992
        - President's House 2.0, 8/18/1992
        - Swofford, 8/19/1993
        - Misc Letters, 8/2/1993
        - Faculty-Admin Gap 1.2, 8/20/1992
        - Photo Essay 1.2, 8/20/1992
        - Internal Comm 1.0, 8/20/1992
        - The Adult University 1.1, 8/20/1992
        - Internal Comm 1.1, 8/20/1992
        - Holcombe-8/92, 8/22/1992
        - Intellectual Change 1.0, 8/22/1992
        - Inglis/Pres House Details, 8/22/1992
        - University Models 1.1, 8/23/1992
        - Sports 2.2, 8/23/1992
        - University Models 1.0, 8/23/1992
        - Plant, 8/24/1992
        - Plant 1.0, 8/24/1992
        - CEC Assignments, 8/25/1992
        - Battle List 1.0, 8/26/1992
        - JJD/GRW/FWW Meeting, 8/26/1992
        - Plant 2.0, 8/28/1992
        - Year Summary, 8/28/1992
        - E-mail 1, 8/3/1992
        - Taubman, 8/3/1992
        - JJD Conv, 8/30/1992
        - Regents-9/92, 8/30/1992
        - Power-8/93, 8/4/1993
        - WLH, 8/9/1992
        - PB-Sports, 8/9/1993
        - Kickoff 1.0, 9/10/1992
        - Faculty Evaluation, 9/15/1992
        - Soup-9/92, 9/15/1992
        - Brown Bags, 9/22/1992
        - Rowe-9/92, 9/22/1992
        - State Layers, 9/22/1992
        - VPR Search, 9/22/1992
        - EO-Deans 1.0, 9/25/1992
        - Autoworld, 9/26/1992
        - Power-9/92, 9/4/1992
        - Fall Issues-92, 9/7/1992
        - Pledge-92, 9/9/1992
        - OUE Support-9/92, 9/9/1992
      - 1993-1994 Write Files, 114 files
        - UG Paradigm, 1/1/1993
        - WAM Preamble, 1/1/1993
        - Transformation Text 1.2, 1/17/1994
        - Transformation Text 1.4, 1/17/1994
        - 25y State App, 1/20/1994
        - % State App, 1/20/1994
        - 10y St Ap/FYES, 1/20/1994
        - All Funds Components, 1/20/1994
        - McTaggart-1/94, 1/20/1994
        - Gen Fund Percentages, 1/20/1994
        - Weidenbach Era, 1/26/1994
        - Trip E-mail, 1/29/1994
        - Vision 2000 2.0, 1/3/1994
        - Models 1.0, 1/4/1994
        - Cosovich-10/11, 10/11/1993
        - EO Comp Memo, 10/13/1993
        - FWW Appointment, 10/24/1993
        - Memo, 10/26/1993
        - SOUP Memo, 10/26/1993
        - Lessons Learned, 10/27/1993
        - Monorail, 10/4/1993
        - Notes-Athena, 10/6/1993
        - Christmas Letter 1.2, 10/7/1993
        - Christmas Letter 1.1, 10/7/1993
        - Deans/EOs #2, 11/1/1993
        - Picture Book Flap, 11/1/1993
        - Op Ed Education, 11/1/1993
        - Transformation Text 1.5, 11/10/1956
        - Computer Notes, 11/11/1993
        - Project Athena 1.01, 11/11/1993
        - Taubman-Found, 11/17/1993
        - Pres Commun, 11/18/1993
        - Christmas Letter 1.4, 11/2/1993
        - Project Athena 2.1, 11/22/1993
        - Project Athena 2.2, 11/22/1993
        - Ryan, 11/24/1993
        - Vision 2017 1.8, 11/25/1993
        - Vision 2017 2.1, 11/25/1993
        - January Regents, 11/29/1993
        - Visitors, 12/10/1993
        - X-mas Letter, 12/11/1993
        - Faculty '93, 12/13/1993
        - AMD/JJD Gift, 12/16/1993
        - Progress Table, 12/22/1993
        - Vision 2000 Appen-I, 12/22/1993
        - Vision 2000 Appen-II, 12/22/1993
        - Peckham Intro, 12/29/1993
        - Diversity Umbrella, 12/29/1993
        - Women 2.3, 12/3/1993
        - Transformation Text 1.0, 12/30/1993
        - Literature and Arts, 12/4/1993
        - Women 3.0, 2/12/1994
        - Deputy Role, 2/14/1994
        - Michigan Agenda Ex Sum 3.0, 2/17/1994
        - White House Draft, 2/2/1994
        - White House-ST, 2/2/1994
        - White House-ST/JJD, 2/2/1994
        - Vision 2017 2.2, 2/21/1994
        - Regents-Vision 2017, 2/27/1994
        - Vision 2017 2.0, 2016
        - Chrysler Center Office, 3/14/1994
        - Nederlander-3/94, 3/14/1994
        - State of Univ 1993, 3/2/1994
        - Sports-Falls Response-Hot, 3/20/1994
        - Sports-Falls Response-Mild, 3/20/1994
        - Bowen-43/94, 3/24/1994
        - Academic Security Council, 3/30/1994
        - GRW-Retirement, 4/2/1994
        - FWW-Retirement, 4/2/1994
        - Nelms-4/94, 4/22/1994
        - Strategic History 2.0, 4/25/1993
        - Strategic History 1.6, 4/25/1993
        - Carol O'Brien, 4/5/1994
        - Comm->Trans Team Memo, 4/7/1994
        - Charge-Faculty, 5/16/1994
        - Charge-Faculty Governance, 5/16/1994
        - Charge-New Markets, 5/16/1994
        - Charge-Process, 5/16/1994
        - Task Force Composition, 5/16/1994
        - Kinnear, 5/18/1994
        - Amster, 5/3/1994
        - Strategic Plan 2017, 6/12/1994
        - Kennedy-6/94, 6/14/1994
        - Renick-6/94, 6/14/1994
        - NAE-6/94, 6/14/1994
        - AMOCO, 7/13/1993
        - City Club, 7/13/1993
        - Obert, 7/13/1993
        - Neal Lane-7/93, 7/15/1993
        - Eng Movers & Shakers, 7/18/1994
        - Cornell Search, 7/18/1994
        - Inglis Supper Group, 7/20/1994
        - EO FY95 Salaries, 7/22/1994
        - Joan-7/94, 7/25/1994
        - Goals-Short, 7/6/1994
        - Magic Bullets, 7/6/1994
        - EO Restructuring, 7/8/1993
        - Sports 2.2, 8/23/1992
        - Mich Agenda Aug Actions, 8/24/1994
        - Project Athena 0.92, 8/25/1993
        - Project Athena 1.0, 8/25/1993
        - Project Athena 1.2, 8/25/1993
        - Strategic Plan 2017 1.1, 8/31/1994
        - EO Salaries-94, 8/9/1994
        - Browne, 9/11/1993
        - Pres Salaries, 9/14/1994
        - AD announcement, 9/2/1993
        - ITD Evolution, 9/21/1993
        - Athena EO Memo, 9/23/1993
        - Project Athena 0.92', 9/23/1993
        - Bylaw Change, 9/24/1993
        - WLH Memo, 9/28/1993
        - WLH Letter, 9/28/1993
        - More History, 9/5/1993
        - Japan-US talk, 9/9/1993
      - 1994-1995 Write Files, 55 files
        - Diversity&Exc 7.1+hist, 10/16/1994
        - DIRECTOR OF PRES EVENTS, 10/23/1994
        - Com List Memo, 10/9/1994
        - MAH-K-12, 10/9/1994
        - EVP-Health Affairs Memo, 11/20/1994
        - Annapolis Talk, 12/18/1994
        - PAG FWW Pres Doc 12/94, 12/21/1994
        - FWW PAG Presentation, 12/21/1994
        - VCM Letter, 12/23/1994
        - 1994-1995 Write Files-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - UM-MSU Statistics, 3/28/1995
        - Chng in FYES/Enroll, 3/30/1995
        - EVPHA Statistics, 3/7/1995